The End
We're here at the Osamu Tezuka Black Jack Exhibition.
If I were to find it, I'd probably spend three hours here alone.
Plenty of time.
I thought it'd be nice to have this on display.
It's on display. Please do it.
Yes, and if you go through this Black Jack exhibition...
You'll see a restaurant called "The Sun and the Moon".
The Sun and the Moon restaurant.
You can enjoy Pinocchio's afternoon tea here!
The restaurant is decorated with pink flowers, Pinocchio's color.
This is the menu...isn't it so cute?
Isn't it super cute?
What do they have here?
Want to take a look?
I'm really into afternoon tea these days.
It's my first afternoon tea.
Really? Your Instagrammer debut?
I was an instagrammer for Shrimp in the Shrimp Club.
It's my debut.
I'm more of a teishoku and ramen kind of guy.
This is my first time at afternoon tea.
Yes, I've been to a lot of afternoon teas.
I'm just trying to decide which one to start with.
I've had a look.
I've been practicing.
Practice? This is what I'm talking about.
What do you mean?What do you mean?
I've been imagining these things.
Wow, they have collaboration drinks and stuff.
There are special drinks.
Pinocollada and
Black and Stormy.
The Pinoccholada is inspired by Pinocchio.
Image?
The Black & Stormy is inspired by Black Jack.
Both are non-alcoholic cocktails
Even children enjoy them
Yes, they are.
Bon appétit.
I'd like to have afternoon tea with this one.
Excuse me.
This is Black and Stormy.
Black.
And this is the Pinocollada cocktail.
Oh, wow.
The Black and Stormy is based on the theme of Black Jack.
with a bit of a spicy cola flavor.
We've prepared it with a taste like a craft cola.
The Pinocorada is a cocktail called a pina colada.
that gives you a sense of cola nuts.
We have a strawberry white cola on the bottom with a pinoko theme.
We have a strawberry white cola on the bottom to give you a taste of the Pinocchio.
We hope you will enjoy it with a swirling glass.
We hope you will enjoy it with a swirling glass. I hope you enjoy your meal.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Shall we eat then?
Bon appétit.
It's inspired by Black Jack's hairstyle.
The white flowers accentuate it.
It's so cute.
I'll go first.
And while you're at it, mix it up.
Mix it up.
What is that?
Adult.
I don't drink black coffee.
What?
That's right.
I can't drink it without milk.
But by having it like this, with ginger ale and lime...
It's like a craft cola.
It's so easy to drink.
It tastes very stylish.
But at the end, you can taste the bitterness of the coffee and the squidgy taste
and a little bitterness of coffee at the end.
Delicious!
Mature taste
with a hint of wind
Delicious Delicious.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
(laughs)
Oh, I thought you were back.
Bon appétit.
Bing bong.
It's so coconutty.
I've been imagining coconut and mushrooms in the bottom.
Strawberry?
The strawberry sauce and coconut go so well together.
The coconut is so refreshing and delicious!
I was left with a bit more sweetness.
It's pretty refreshing.
Your hair is pink!
It's a great match!
Pink saint!
It's so cute!
Yay!
If you come here, please wear pink hair.
Okay, well, here you go.
Is this Anpanman's hair?
Yes, it's Anpanman.
Wow, it's so high!
So high!
I can see Tokyo Tower and Sky Tree from here.
Pinoko Tower is standing in the middle of them.
About Pinocchio's Pink Afternoon, Pinocchio's pink-themed acrylics will be displayed. About Pinocchio's Pink AfternoonsPinocchio's Pink Themed Acrylic Decorations
The top four tiers will be 8 types of sweet desserts and
The bottom two tiers will be four types of meal savories.
May I ask you to go once?
Yes, thank you.
It's so pretty.
I want to see it from over here.
Oh, it's so cute!
It's so cute.
And don't forget about the block jacks, sir.
ActionBully, beautiful!
That's close.
Cute.
Now, I'm going to have some!
Bon appétit.
Where is the right place to go?
Which way is the right way?
Well, I always go from the top because I don't know.
Is it better to go from the top?
I don't know.
You want me to Google it?
Yeah, once.
Google it once?
How to Eat Afternoon Tea
It's important at first, because you're a beginner.
Yeah, I always eat at random. You're right, I always eat just fine.
Have your own instincts.
This is perfect, and I can return the mannerisms of the afternoon tea.
Thank you.
The site is Mr. Everybody's Food!
Thank you very much. I'll refer to it.
I don't have any rules for this.
It is preferable to eat from light-colored and light-flavored food
Hardly, it is not so.
Which one is light in color?
Of course you have to eat the most flavorful ones last.
Well, isn't it hard to say which is lighter in color?
Can I see something?
Do you see any lighter ones?
Oh, this one?
Like this pinocchio parfait.
It's got a lot of white in it.
Isn't it hard to say "light"?
What kind of light?
What do you mean, "thin"?
I'll start with what I think is cheap.
Okay.
It's too thick, for sure.
Not too thin?
When you put them together like this, if they were paints, this one would be better.
That's...
Yeah. Come on.
Can I take it? Can I take it?
I'll just use my shattered cell phone.
Yeah, sure, I'll just get the screen.
I'm an idol.
I'm a pudding.
And you're a...
Cream parfait.
I have beet and soy milk potage
Mini shot glasses
This is definitely too salty.
It's the morning, after all.
We're not having afternoon tea today.
It's Good Morning Tea.
Bon appétit!
So cute!
What a Pinocchio!
I don't want to ruin it.
It's too cute.
Smooth milk pudding. Delicious.
I could eat Delhi and pudding together.
I like it. You know, when I was a kid, it was...
When you were a kid, it was either delhi or pudding.
It's either one or the other. It's the whole one or the other.
You can have both.
It's good. It's mild.
Bon appétit.
So, the shot glasses mean you're just gonna drink it like that?
Yes, I do. Yup.
Beet and Soy Milk Potage
Mini shot glasses
Bon appétit!
Yeah, healthy taste
Beets
What a great sudden healthy feeling!
I'm awake.
The color, beets, they're so beautiful.
But the taste is so gentle.
Very gentle.
They may be dark, but they taste tender.
You passed.
It passes the test, doesn't it? This one.
Afternoon.
Pinocchio!
So, I'd like to have the choux cream puffs from Militokosis.
This way.
Yup.
Militokosis cream puffs
Cream puffs
Terrelette.
How do you like it?
It's good! Delicious!
Tasty?
Maybe it's too rich. It's so good!
Chestnuts.
Chestnuts are nice. And it's very autumnal.Chestnuts are nice. And it's so autumnal.
The cream inside the chestnuts is so nice and creamy.
Such a small thing. I suddenly felt satisfied.
It's good.
Wow, this is delicious.
I knew that all of the creams at the restaurant were delicious.
Yes, it is.
Next, one more time.
I also enjoy this shu kijii.
Since we are here,
I would like to have the Lac-Jac 50th Anniversary Canulé.
See?
So cute.
I can't eat this, so I'll leave it.
I eat these things one by one because I don't want to waste them.
I understand.
Bon appétit.
How is it?
The texture is moist, and the canele is sticky and delicious.
Raspberry on top?
Yes.
It's covered with a sauce, which is also sweet and tasty.
Nice, it's coated with chocolate.
Yes, it is.
Looks delicious.
I love canele.
Cannelles are delicious, aren't they?
Can I go on and on with my greed? Are you sure you don't mind if I go on and on with my greed?
Are we done? Don't worry about it.
Then I'll have the strawberry mousse.
Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
Mousse is good.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
It's good. Maybe it's just the right amount.
Yeah, it is.
It looks like a lot, but it's all in one bite.
Then I'll have some too.
I thought it would be light in color, but I guess it was a little salty.
I'll have this.
Is this shrimp mousse?
Shrimp mousse,
Mushimushi daikon color.
Suddenly.
Mushimushidaikon color.
Shrimp mousse.
27.
So you're making the daikon radish red, too?
Yes, all in daikon color.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It's a mousse, but it has the flavor of shrimp and salt,
It's just right. Just right.
If I ate too much, I'd eat something salty, but it's so perfect.
It's delicious.
The seasoning is very elegant, overall.
See, why not, it's Roppongi, isn't it?
That's right.
It's Roppongi in Minato-ku.
It's Roppongi in Ominato-ku.
It is Roppongi, isn't it?
That's classy,
It really is the height of classy.
It's on the 52nd floor, right now.
The view is amazing.
It's really beautiful.
We're looking out over Tokyo.
Yes, it is.
If you go that way..,
Oh, hey, Mt. Fuji.
Fuji.
We could see it, couldn't we?
You have a great panoramic view.
I'm looking forward to the view.
It's luxurious.
It enriches my heart,
Look at this Roppongi,
I feel like my body is happy, I feel like my body is happy because of your mouth,
It's great, isn't it?
It's a beautiful morning, we're having a beautiful morning.
We're about to have a nice morning.
I'm glad we got up early.
I'm glad.
Let's see what we're going to eat next.
I'll share this with you.
Let's see, cake?
Mushroom achiomri cake.
Rare cheesecake.
So cute.
Cute.
Achimliquette.
What's achiomuriket?
Is it written like this?
Achimuriket.
Bon appétit.
I heard a crunch.
How is it?
The sauce is crispy.
Strawberry and cheesecake inside.
It's rich. Cheesecake is very rich.
It's cheesecake.
It's so rich and delicious.
Bon appétit.Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Thanks for looking.
It's delicious.
Winner.
Yummy.
And the cheese isn't too cheesy.
It's easy to stretch.
It's delicious.
This is pretty good right now.
This is delicious.
It's a contender.
The colors are all pretty.
It's pink.
The partopini is so buttery.
I love it!
Yeah, I love it!
This is my favorite.
Yum!
It's so good.
Matchoise cake is so good!
Afternoon tea is fun!
It's fun, isn't it?
I don't know where to start.
But it doesn't matter who you are.
So, today I'd like to introduce you to
You're going to Black Jack's.You've been to Black Jack's.
And also had afternoon tea.
How was it, Mie?
Thank you for coming to our event, Mae.
Thank you for inviting me.
It was a pleasure to have you at the event.
I was happy to be able to go with you.
It was fun and delicious.
If you ever go there again, please come this way!
Yeah.
I'm sure it will taste even better if you eat it and tell me what you thought and how much fun it was.
I think the food will be even better if you eat it while talking about how much fun you had.
Of course, fans of my works
I'm sure that the fans of your works will enjoy the food even more.
And also, there are a lot of things that can be easily displayed at afternoon tea.
There are a lot of things that can be easily displayed at afternoon tea.
Even if you don't know the artwork
even if you don't know the work.
I hope you'll be interested in reading the original manga
I hope you will be interested in reading the original manga.
So, we are
We're still going to eat.
But once here...
Let's end with Pinocchio's famous line.
Ready?
Anchovinke! t